



horrigueouss@gmail.com



+48 504 741 811



linkedin.com/in/oussama-horrigue-69624b1b7



https://oussamahorrigue.github.io/

## Summary

I strongly believe that our life experience is enriched by the diversity of our experiences. The modern world presents excellent opportunities to study, work and travel across the globe experiencing rich cultures and collaborating with people to succeed together. I have actively capitalized on such opportunities over a relatively short period.

I have built a wide skillset during my educational career. I completed my BSc in Sciences and Technology with a minor in Electronics and computer sciences from the University of Monastir in Tunisia and Poland from the Polytechnic University of Bialystok as an Erasmus+ student in the last semester of my B.Sc. degree from 2018 to 2021. Taking courses in Mathematics, Physics, Electronics, computer sciences, telecommunications, mechanical, Mechatronics engineering, and management offered a comprehensive understanding of the modern workplace. I then decided to specialize in Mechatronics engineering through a Master's from the Polytechnic University of Bialystok with a specialty in Intelligent Production Systems (IPS). Then I decided to continue my master's in Germany at the Technical University of Kaiserslautern as an exchange student in which I am currently involved. The fact that I have studied in foreign countries with foreign languages allowed me to develop essential skills of teamwork, leadership, and communication in international contexts.

## **Experience**



### Software Engineer

Aexol

Mar 2022 - Aug 2022 (6 months)

# φ Research And Development Specialist

Bialystok University of Technology

Nov 2021 - Feb 2022 (4 months)

Autonomous Systems Synthesis and Analysis Based on Unmanned Aeriel Vehicles:

- Simulation and testing control algorithms for autonomous systems.
- · Vision-Based localization, environment recognition, and Machine learning techniques.
- Image Processing Integration.

#### Summer Internship

Intelligent System Engineering - INSEN Jun 2020 - Aug 2020 (3 months)

#### **Education**



## University of Kaiserslautern

Master's degree, Mechatronics, Robotics, and Automation Engineering Sep 2022 - Jul 2023

# (坤/ Bialystok University of Technology

Master's degree, Mechatronics, Robotics, and Automation Engineering Feb 2022 - Sep 2022

## (中) Bialystok University of Technology

Mar 2021 - Jul 2021

Sixth semester of Bsc as an exchange student passed with a First Class distinction.

- Artificial Intelligence
- Internet of Things
- Antennas and Propagation
- Modern Control of Mechatronics Systems
- Programmable Logic Controllers
- High Voltage Technique



#### ISIMM | High Institute of Informatics and Mathematics of Monastir

Bachelor's degree, Computer Sciences and Electronics

2018 - Feb 2021

This training allowed me to master the software development processes by relying on modeling, design, development, and IT project management techniques. These techniques allow the design of modern applications, requiring the integration of heterogeneous components (connection to a database, network communication, and graphical interface for example).

This diploma gave me an excellent education in my field. The main skills acquired are:

- · Network systems administration and security
- electronics and components
- · Database administration
- Web programming
- · computer data transmission services
- radio and television broadcasting networks (terrestrial, satellite, cable network)
- · computer equipment, servers, computer hardware, computers, and software
- Computer architecture
- Data transmission
- Advanced algorithm and data structure

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



CS50 - Harvard University

#### Skills

Tailwind CSS • Git • MATLAB • Python (Programming Language) • Flask • Databases • Web Applications • Robot Operating System (ROS) • Next.js • TypeScript